I've been wondering. You said
it was working when you moved in.
(Leonard:)It was. But one night
Sheldon came home from work....
[VIDEO GAME NOISES ON TV]
(Past Sheldon:)What is going on here?
Hey, this is Howard and Raj.
They work at the university too.
(Past Leonard:)-Hey.
-Hey.
(Past Sheldon:)I'll get to you later.
(Past Sheldon:)What are you sitting on?
(Past Howard:)I can't speak for these guys,
but I'm sitting on my tushy. Heh, heh.
(Past Howard:)-It's a joke.
-Not a good idea.
-"Tushy" is "buttocks," right?
-Right.
Heh. Hilarious. Heh, heh.
(Past Sheldon:)Explain the couch.
There were people on the first floor
who were moving out and sold it for $100.
(Past Leonard:)-Howard and Raj helped me bring it up.
-What's wrong with the furniture we have?
[TURNS OFF VIDEO GAME]
They are lawn chairs.
(Past Leonard:)There was no place for company.
(Past Sheldon:)Did it occur to you that was by design?